{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct option",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M2L10b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "img pants",
                    "options": [
                        "Boys",
                        "Girls",
                        "Both",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "img socks",
                    "options": [
                        "Boys",
                        "Girls",
                        "Both",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "img skirt",
                    "options": [
                        "Boys",
                        "Girls",
                        "Both",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "img sweater",
                    "options": [
                        "Boys",
                        "Girls",
                        "Both",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Complete the questions about your store. Choose yes or no.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP2M5L23b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "__ any ham?",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Is there any",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__  ",
                    "options": [
                        "yes",
                        "no",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ a carrot?",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Is there a",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "yes",
                        "no",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ plums?",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Is there a",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "yes",
                        "no",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__ milk?",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Is there any",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "yes",
                        "no",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}